<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Space blog!</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/My-Blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Space blog!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.132.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 19:33:31 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/My-Blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2st law of behavior change</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/My-Blog/posts/2stlawofhabits/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 19:33:31 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/My-Blog/posts/2stlawofhabits/</guid>
      <description>2st law: Make it attractive We humans are prone to liking exaggerated versions of reality, for example, junk food. One of the main goals of food science is to make products more appealing to consumers. Not only that, look around: pornography with stimulating scenes at a rate is impossible to produce in real life; Social media offers more like and compliments than you get for your work; photo editing, advertising, fashion (not even the model looks like herself in the final image); Catchy titles, etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1st law of behavior change</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/My-Blog/posts/1slawofhabits/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 15:39:53 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/My-Blog/posts/1slawofhabits/</guid>
      <description>Make it clear for good habits, make it invisible for bad habits Before delving into the techniques, understand: your habits become automatic and end up being unconscious actions. In other words, you don&amp;rsquo;t need to be aware of the stimulus for the habit to begin. This is what makes habits useful and dangerous.
Before building new habits, you must be aware of your current ones. Point and talk: Method used by Japan to reduce errors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atomic Habits</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/My-Blog/posts/atomics-habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 18:52:31 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/My-Blog/posts/atomics-habits/</guid>
      <description>Reading Atomic Habits, James Clear’s best seller, I learn several lessons to build good habits and break bad ones. The most important thing about habits is your habits system. A good system allows you to improve 1% every day and makes you 37x better a year. If you want results, achieve your goals, you need to focus on your habits system.
How to change my behavior? There are three levels that changes could happen:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autodesenvolvimento e por que comecei esse blog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/My-Blog/posts/why-i-started-a-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 18:45:24 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/My-Blog/posts/why-i-started-a-blog/</guid>
      <description>POV: você está perdido
O começo. Recentemente, em maio desse ano, entrei na onda do autodesenvolvimento. 19 anos, desempregado sem experiência profissional relevante, cursando computação sem saber se era o que eu realmente queria, sem namorada, amigos presentes e recém recuperado das minhas crises esquizofrênicas de um ano atrás - perdi meu primeiro emprego como analista de ti jr, uma amizade que achava importante (talvez isso foi a melhor coisa que ocorreu), minha dignidade, minha sanidade e minha vontade de viver.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
